<VersionInfo>
  <CurrentLatestVersion>23.6.23.1</CurrentLatestVersion>
  <Releases>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.23.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Link to Beginner's Guide to Group Soaring Flights</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This version adds an option to include a predefined or custom link to some existing guide for beginners that want to learn how to join the group soaring events.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.19.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Small required fixes</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Prevent posting files without the session being saved.
        Fixed recommended add-ons sometimes not reseting when loading a different file.
        Fixed possible errors when clicking post buttons with empty information.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.13.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Share a group event for a task</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        When creating a group event, it's nice to share it directly in the task's thread, so now you can.
        This release also adds a new club and fixes one or two small details.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.6.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Version info files now on GitHub</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The location of XML files containing version information has been changed to be directly on GitHub, improving the release pipeline and workflow.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.6.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fixed error when impossible to check for latest version</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This releases fixes a bug for some people that cannot reach the server to check for latest version.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.5.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fixed loading shared DPHX</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This releases fixes a bug when loading a shared or downloaded DPHX file
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.4.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fixed briefing altitudes (wrong units)</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This releases fixes a bug on the briefing tab that was displaying altitudes with the wrong units
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.04.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fixed a bug when saving a file for the first time</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This releases fixes a bug that prevented saving a new file.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.30.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Save process revisited and more</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release changes how saving a session works:
        - It now detects when changes are pending (Save button turns red)
        - It now reopens the last file (if there's one) between runs
        - It now always saves a DPHX package

        But this release also contains other changes:
        - Other improvements to wizard guide (it now asks where you want to go between sections)
        - Fix the Country area where buttons are not enabled at the right time (move up, down, remove)
        - Save window location and size after each use
        - Small fixes here and there
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.26.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Discord Markdown to enhance all posts</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release mostly focuses on the addition of Discord Markdown to enhance all posts in Discord
        - Improvements and fixes to the wizard guide to include the briefing tab
        - Added airports ICAO to list of waypoints in the Discord post (useful when more than departure and arrival airports in the flight plan)
        - Added short description to briefing, between task title and credits
        - Fixed wrong ICAO codes in the waypoints grid on the briefing page and support more than two ICAO in the waypoints
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.24.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Discord emojies and more briefing improvements</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release includes:
        - Discord emojies to section titles in the posts content
        - New Weather tab on briefing to display wind and cloud layers in grid formats like waypoints
        - Fixed guide tooltip not closing when hitting F1 on the new Discord tab
        - Fixed event info and add-ons info not reloading properly in the briefing when going in and out of the Units tab
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.24.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Briefing improvements</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release mostly features improvements to the briefing tab.
        - Added mouse drag support on map and other images
        - Added country flag support in the briefing viewer
        - Added global exception handling (in case of crashes)
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.19.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Preferred units on Briefing page</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Most important feature added with this release is the support for preferred display units on the Briefing page.
        But this release also includes:
        - Inclusion of meters per second for wind speeds
        - Downgrade of the .Net requirements to 4.8 which should make the tool run on more Windows versions
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.18.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Small fix for bug on extra files introduced by previous version</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This is a quick fix for a bug related to the storage of extra files.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.17.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Major redesign of the window AND new features</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The main feature of this release is a big revamping of the interface, to try and make the user experience easier and also accomodate new fields.
        - Removed the “resulting text” fields on the right to make room for other input fields and possibly make the form fit on smaller screens.
        - Whole new section for the recommended add-ons (with links) for the task, no need to put that in the description anymore.
        - Added a section to include the DPHX package with the files to promote sharing it.
        - Changed the order of the posts so that files come first in the thread.
        - Adjusted the wizard (guide) for the major redesign of the form and the new features.
        - New Add-Ons tab within the briefing to list recommendeded add-ons. Double-click the URL to open it.
        - Several other small fixes and adjustments were also made along the way
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.11.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>New compass roses for each wind layer</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The main feature of this release is the addition of graphical compass roses with wind indication for each layer on the briefing's map tab.
        It also contains a fix to properly handle images when switching back and forth from the briefing tab.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.8.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Event is not always enabled and included now</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Since not all tasks are events, a checkbox has been added to specifically include an event into the DPH file.
        Also, clicking the "Thermal" checkbox now also activates the "Sync Fly" option on the event tab.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.4.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Revamped Briefing Event Info with Countdowns</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The Event Info section of the Briefing tab now contains several countdown fields to the various event timings.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.2.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Support resizing and scrollbars</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The window can now be resized and scrollbars are available when screen space is limited.
        The Briefing tab now displays event information (Event Info tab)
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.1.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Bunch of fixes related to regional number formats</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release focuses only on problems that were related to different number formatting based on regional settings.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.1.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Preventing crashes and new waypoint columns</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Try to prevent some crashes with the retrieval of countries from geolocation using waypoints coordinates.
        Check minimum .NET Framework requirement during startup
        Add several new waypoint distances columns with drop down list (briefing tab, waypoints)
        Add possiblity to show/hide the latitude and longitude columns (briefing tab, waypoints)
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.28.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Revamping of Briefing tab</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release merges with the DPHX Unpack and Load tool and replaces the old Briefing tab with the same one built for that tool.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.24.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Small fix following previous update</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        See previous release for more information.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.24.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Known Clubs now in XML file</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Known Clubs informations are now stored in an external XML file.

        Reverted Daylight Saving Time code to Zulu only, with warning visible when DST applies for the selected event date.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.18.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Multiple country flags and autoload countries</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The tool now supports adding multiple country flags to be added to the task and event titles.

        The countries are now also automatically added based on the flight plan's waypoints.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.17.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Country Flags and known clubs name change</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        New field to specify Country flag to use in the task's title

        Several known clubs have changed their names, this update implements the new names.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.16.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Bug fix for cloud layer altitude</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The cloud layer altitude was reversed between meters and feet.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.2.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Briefing tab improvements</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Minor improvements to the briefing tab to remove waypoints from the description and make sure formatting (bold and italic) are properly applied.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.2.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fix for SSC channel name and remove gust warning</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Minor update to update the name of the voice channel for SSC Saturday's group flight and also remove the wind gusts warning as it appears to be resolved in SU12.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.3.20.4</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Auto-Update bug fix</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Fixed bug where Updater did not actually extract the files.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.3.20.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Auto-Update implementation</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Starting with this release, an auto-update feature has been implemented and the app will automatically check for a new release when you start it.

        If it finds one, it will show you a popup window with the release's details and the release history too. You then have the choice to update or not, but if you do, everything will happen automatically.

        Manual update will still be possible by downloading the latest release and replacing the files yourself.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.3.20.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Yet another fix for daylight saving time calculation</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Very minor update that should fix the daylight saving date and time calculation for good.

        Let me know if you think there is still a problem with that.

        To update: simply overwrite your current files with the one in this release.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.3.13.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>DPHX Package creation and load back</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        In this new version, the "Create package" button becomes "Share package" and instead of only copying files to a folder for you to manually zip, it will now put all the required files into a .dphx file, save it and place it on your clipboard. You can then paste the file anywhere (email, Discord, other chat platforms, etc.) to share with someone else.

        Of course, anyone with the tool can then also load back the .dphx file (when you click load, you can select both .dph and .dphx files) and automatically extract all the same files including the .dph file and load everything easily.

        The tool also supports direct opening by double-clicking on a dphx file once you associate the file extension with the tool's main executable.

        To update, simply overwrite your existing files with the ones in this release.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.3.12.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fix for Daylight Saving rules to calculate UTC and local times</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        After going into DST here in East America, I've discovered a bug with the UTC and Local date/time conversions. This release should address this problem.

        Simply overwrite your existing files with the one in this release.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.3.10.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Small release</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        In this release:
        - The airfield database is no longer used as we always take the airfield names from the flight plan file
        - The waypoint coordinates for xbox no longer contain a comma, but just a space
        - Fixed a possible bug where the default clubs were not loaded
        You can delete the csv file of the airfield database that was included in previous versions. Simply overwrite the other files.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.3.6.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Rename, split, add waypoint coordinates</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        For this release, you should delete any previous files you had and replace them by the ones in this release.
        - The main executable was renamed to DiscordPostHelper.exe
        - The code not directly related to UI has been moved into a CommonLibrary.dll

        New features:
        - The extra files section now do not accept potentially harmful file extensions
        - There is a new checkbox to add all waypoint coordinates into the description to help Xbox users
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.2.26.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Version 23.2.26.1 - New Briefing Tab</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release adds a new "Briefing" tab, where will you find all relevant information to give during the briefing time.

        The tab is itself divided into two sub-tabs, the "Basic Info" and the "Flight and Map" where you get to select an image from the extra files, that represents the flight map. You can then zoom and scroll the image according to the briefing needs.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.2.24.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Version 23.2.24.2 Unix timestamps fixes</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Bug fix in this release:
        - During refactoring, an error was introduced with the syntax of the Unix timestamps, it is now fixed

        Simply download the ZIP file from the asset, unzip in a new folder anywhere or over your previous version and launch the executable.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.2.22.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Version 23.2.22.1 Load parameter file</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        New features in this release:
        - You can now set Windows to auto-launch the tool when double-clicking a .dph file, it will be automatically opened
        - The current session file is added to the window title for convenience

        Simply download the ZIP file from the asset, unzip in a new folder anywhere or over your previous version and launch the executable.

        To set Windows to automatically open the app when double-clicking on a .dph file, you will need to right-click a .dph file and select "Open with..." or double-click the .dph file, and then browse and select the executable file and set to "Always".
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.2.20.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Version 23.2.20.1 Code refactoring and cleanup</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Several fixes or improvements along the way, including performance wise.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
  </Releases>
</VersionInfo>