<VersionInfo>
  <CurrentLatestVersion>23.10.5.2</CurrentLatestVersion>
  <Releases>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.10.5.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Remove the wath symbol and sync with DPH tool</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Removed the invalid watch symbol from the empty Main Task Info in the Briefing control.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.10.3.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Gate Diameter or Radius</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Added a new option to display gate sizes as Diameter or Radius.
        Fixed the caption and status bar not displaying the current filename.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.9.29.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Smarter and smarter</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Remember the last loaded DPHX file between sessions.
        Added the ability to detect if all the files are already in their destinations to highlight or not "Unpack" and display a status message.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.9.27.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Small release to stay in-sync with DPH Tool</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        When clicking the button to open the task's thread, try to open on Discord app directly then fall back to browser if it didn't work.
        Fixed duration text when no min or max specified or only one of them or both are the same.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.9.19.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Several unrelated but relatively substantial improvements</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Opening B21 Task Planner now passes both the PLN and WPR files if they're both present.
        Added button to bring you in the right Discord thread to post a task result, screenshot, track file, etc.
        When barometric pressure is not standard, added a warning symbol to remind people to press "B" or manually adjust it in their glider.
        Added more support for Discord's markdown codes and improved the briefing's text content.
        Removed the “No Gust” info when no gust is present.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.8.28.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Cleanup, resync, rename club</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Renamed club "GG-💎" to "💎 Tuesday" and added "💎 Sunday" (both EDT and EST).
        Clean up of the clubs and resync all libraries.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.8.21.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Test audio button and added main area/POI</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Added "Test" button to test output volume of audio cues.
        Added the main area / POI to the task description on the briefing.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.8.17.3</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Audio Cues for countdowns on briefing's event tab</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This version adds audio cues for all countdowns on the briefing's event tab, allowing to hear the countdowns without having to look at the tool's window.
        It is also possible to adjust the output volume of these audio cues.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.8.15.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>MSFS Local times in relation to event times</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This version adds the MSFS local times in relation to the event times (sync, launch, start) to the briefing's event info.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.29.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Change to the auto-update process</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The auto-update program is now a Windows form with better formatting.
        Also, the updater now displays all release notes between user's version and newest version available.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.6.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Version info files now on GitHub</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The location of XML files containing version information has been changed to be directly on GitHub, improving the release pipeline and workflow.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.6.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fixed error when impossible to check for latest version</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This releases fixes a bug for some people that cannot reach the server to check for latest version.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.6.4.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fixed briefing altitudes (wrong units)</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This releases fixes a bug on the briefing tab that was displaying altitudes with the wrong units
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.26.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Short description and small fixes</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release includes:
        - Added short description to briefing, between task title and credits
        - Fixed wrong ICAO codes in the waypoints grid on the briefing page and support more than two ICAO in the waypoints
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.24.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>More briefing improvements</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release includes:
        - New Weather tab on briefing to display wind and cloud layers in grid formats like waypoints
        - Allow only one instance of the program to run at a time
        - Fixed event info and add-ons info not reloading properly in the briefing when going in and out of the Units tab
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.22.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Briefing improvements</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release mostly features improvements to the briefing tab.
        - Added mouse drag support on map and other images
        - Added country flag support in the briefing viewer
        - Added button to open the B21 Online Task Planer with the current flight plan
        - Added global exception handling (in case of crashes)
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.19.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Preferred units to display most data</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Most important feature added with this release is the support for preferred display units on the Briefing page.
        But this release also includes:
        - Inclusion of meters per second for wind speeds
        - Downgrade of the .Net requirements to 4.8 which should make the tool run on more Windows versions
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.18.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Small fix for bug on extra files introduced by previous version</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This is a quick fix for a bug related to the storage of extra files.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.17.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>New Add-ons tab</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release focuses on the addition of the Add-ons tab to list recommendeded add-ons. Double-click the URL to open it.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.16.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Fix Flight Plan folder not working in Settings</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        When trying to set the flight plan folder in Settings, it would change the default DPHX Packages instead.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.11.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>New compass roses for each wind layer</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The main feature of this release is the addition of graphical compass roses with wind indication for each layer.
        It also contains a fix to properly clear up the images being used by the tool when reloading a file.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.8.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Adjustments related to the event now being optional</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release contains no visible changes or fixes, but small adjustments were needed due to the event now being optional in the DPH file.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.4.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Revamped Briefing Event Info with Countdowns</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The Event Info section of the Briefing tab now contains several countdown fields to the various event timings.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.2.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Event Information now displayed</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        The Event Info tab now displays event information
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.1.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Bunch of fixes related to regional number formats</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release focuses only on problems that were related to different number formatting based on regional settings.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.5.1.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Check minimum requirement and new waypoint columns</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Check minimum .NET Framework requirement during startup
        Add several new waypoint distances columns with drop down list (briefing tab, waypoints)
        Add possiblity to show/hide the latitude and longitude columns (briefing tab, waypoints)
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.28.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Lots of new stuff and bux fixes</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Added XCSoar .tsk files support
        Added task credits under the task title
        Added support for displaying other images included in package
        Added support for right-click on paths in the settings page to open up the actual folder in Windows Explorer
        Added cleanup of temporary folder at start and close
        Fix for files not loading from the right folder
        Lots of bug fixes around loading different dphx packages in the same session
        Fix conversions to integer or not doing proper round up/down
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.27.2</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>Testing the auto-update</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        This release is only to test the auto-update feature.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
    <Release>
      <ReleaseVersion>23.4.27.1</ReleaseVersion>
      <ReleaseTitle>First BETA Release</ReleaseTitle>
      <ReleaseNotes>
        Open BETA Release.
        Contains minimum features for real testing purposes.
      </ReleaseNotes>
    </Release>
  </Releases>
</VersionInfo>